

NHU THI THANH TAM

Tester

Dong Da, Hanoi

OBJECTIVE

Short term: With experience in the software field with the main role as a tester (web testing, API, SQL), I would like to work in a dynamic environment. Studying, absorbing knowledge and experiences from colleagues to enhance my qualifications.

Long term: Become a Middle and Senior Tester for the next two years, and a test leader for the next three to four years.

EDUCATION

Academy Of Finance

Management Information System.

2020 - 2024

2023

Vietnam Tester Training Academy

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

Testcases, test plan

• SQL

Agile/Scrum

Java, C#

Bug report

Jira

Postman, Jmeter

• Gitlab, Github, Fork

06/2024 - Present

WORK EXPERIENCE

BKSOFT 06/2023 - Present

Tester | Banking

Project Description: Bank web application to manage SeABank branches

- Team size: 8
- Responsibilities: Agent branch management module, associate management module, checking account opening records management module
 - Communicate teammates to clarify requirement
 - Create testcase, execute test
 - Use SQL query statements
 - Create Q&A for developer
 - Log bugs in Jira and daily report
- Tool: Postman (API), Jmeter (Performance), Jira, PostgreSQL, GG Sheet

Tester | E-commerce

02/2024 - 05/2024

- Project Description: Buy books online website
- Team size: 6
- Responsibilities: Category management module, product management module, order management module
 - Study requirement and make Q&A to clarify
 - Create testcase, execute test
 - Find and report defect, clarify defect with developer
 - Log bugs in Jira, verify them for each release
- Tool: Postman (API), Jmeter (Performance), MySQL, Jira, GG Sheet

Tester | CRM 10/2023 - 01/2024

- Project Description: CRM web application for supplier management and import management
- Team size: 9
- Responsibilities: Supplier management module, goods management module
 - Analyze requirements
 - Create testcase, execute test
 - Log, report and tracking defects
 - Daily report to PM
- Tool: Postman (API), Jmeter (Performance), SQL Server, Excel, Jira

Backend Developer | Onsite Viettel Project

08/2023 - 09/2023

- Measure network and antenna signals.
- Connect HTTP Server and HTTP Client to call APIs.
- Create interface on C# Winform.

Backend Developer | Work Management Project

06/2023 - 07/2023

- Manage projects and work according to the EAV model.
- Implemented CRUD APIs, import data from Excel file API.
- Used Postman to test APIs.

HOBBIES ————— LANGUAGES —————

- Data analysis
- Technology research
- Vietnamese
- English (Basics)